what is going on everybody welcome to
到底是怎么回事 大家欢迎
the 10th Cavey tutorial video in this
在这 第十个 Cavey教程视频
video we're gonna be talking about the
视频我们要去谈论 的
screen manager so I've already talked
屏幕管理员， 所以我 已经说过了
about this what the purpose of the
这个什么的目的
screen manager is in the last video so
屏幕管理器是在最后一个视频所以
we're just going to go ahead and hop
我们将 继续前进并跳跃
right on into it so to get the screen
直接进入它 ，以获得屏幕
manager we have to make another import
我们必须再次进口
and this one's going to be from TV UI x
而这一次将 是 从电视UI X
dot screen manager import screen manager
点屏幕管理器导入屏幕管理器
we're gonna also need screen and then
我们还需要屏幕，然后
we're gonna import fade transition so
我们要进口淡出过渡等等
not only is it going to allow us to
这不仅会让 我们做到
change between screens there's a quite
屏幕之间的变化是相当的
well there's a handful of transitions
还有一些过渡
that you can use that just kind of makes
您 可以使用 ， 只是一种使
it look a little better as you
它看起来 好像你一样
transition and it literally a transition
过渡，它实际上是一个过渡
helps the user know that transition is
帮助用户知道过渡
even occurring right but it's also it's
即使发生的权利，但它也是
just more user friendly and it looks
只是更多的用户友好，它看起来
better so anyway those are the things
无论如何，这些都是好事
that we need and now we're ready to
我们需要， 现在我们准备好了
actually build our application luckily
真幸运地建立我们的应用程序
or at least for this tutorial we can do
或者至少对于 我们可以做的 这个 教程
it pretty simply we're just going to
它非常简单，我们只是要
need a lot of classes that happen to
需要大量的类， 碰巧
pass but anyways first we're gonna have
但 首先 我们会有的
a class and we're gonna have a main
一个班，我们会有一个主要的
screen and main screen is going to
屏幕和主屏幕会
inherit from screen basically to use a
从 屏幕上 继承 基本上 使用一个
screen manager we need to import from
屏幕经理，我们需要从导入
screen and inherit from screen rather
屏幕并从屏幕继承
and then so main screen will pass then
然后使主屏幕上会通过，则
we're gonna have class another screen
我们要上另一个屏幕
again it's going to inherit from screen
它也将从屏幕继承
and again it's just gonna pass and then
再一次它会 通过然后
we'll have class screen manage
我们将有班级屏幕管理
management it's really easy to koi
管理它真的很容易koi
when you're like doing tutorials or just
当你喜欢做教程或只是
like trying to learn about something
就像试图了解 某事
it's really easy to make the function
做这个功能 真的很容易
named the same thing as what you're
命名与你的相同
working with either a module or exactly
与模块一起工作或 准确地工作
this because generally they name their
这是因为他们通常会将其命名
things a pretty intuitive name as well
事情也是一个非常直观的名字
so you can get in all kinds of trouble
所以你可以在各种 惹上 麻烦
anyway screen manager don't do that so
无论如何，屏幕管理器不这样 做
this will be a screen management class
这将是一个屏幕管理类
which we'll cover in just a moment and
我们稍后会介绍和
then it's going to inherit from screen
那么它将 从屏幕 继承
manager which is here
这是经理
you guessed it it's gonna pass okay so
你猜对了，它会过得 很好
we don't really need any logic at this
我们并不真正需要 在这个 任何逻辑
point simply because we are really just
只是因为我们真的 是公正的
doing like the visual and keavy kind of
像视觉和重力一样
stuff at this point so we don't actually
在这一点上的东西，所以我们不实际
need to put any logic here but soon you
需要把这里的任何逻辑，但很快你
can imagine you might and that's
可以想象你可能会那样
basically it
基本上它
although we need to get rid of these
尽管我们需要摆脱这些
right here so presentation is not a
这里介绍所以不是
function it's just a variable so we're
函数它只是一个变量， 所以我们
going to go ahead and get rid of that
要继续前进， 摆脱 那
and now we're ready to move into our kv
现在我们准备好 进入我们的KV了
file so we'll save that there and we'll
文件， 所以我们将保存 在那里，我们会
come over to our ki v file and I'm just
过来我们的 ki v文件，我只是
going to go ahead and delete everything
将继续并 删除所有内容
out of this main kv we don't really need
出于这个主要的 kv我们并不 需要
anything there and if ya I'm gonna
任何东西，如果 我会去的
delete okay so now that we want to do is
删除 好吧，现在我们 想要 做的是
we want to utilizes meet or fade
我们想要利用会面或淡入淡出
transition and later on you can actually
过渡和后来你可以实际上
you might do something with it but
你可能会用 它做点什么， 但是
actually probably the main use of fade
实际上可能主要是使用淡入淡出
transitions going to be in the key V
过渡将在关键V中
file anyways but so to do it import in
反正文件，但这样做 导入
your ki V file it's really quite simple
你的ki V文件真的很简单
but I guess it's it's kind of flipped
但我想这是它的翻转
around
周围
but anyway it's kind of I'll just show
但无论如何，这只是我会展示的
you so we want to import what we want to
你所以我们想要导入我们想要的东西
import fade transition and then from
导入淡入淡出过渡，然后从
where so key v UI x dot screen manager
那么 关键v UI x点屏幕 管理器
dot fade transition okay and that's our
点褪色过渡没关系 ，这就是我们的
import that's really the only thing we
导入这真的是我们唯一的事情
need to right there now we're gonna
现在需要在那里， 我们会去的
reference first screen management and
参考第一个屏幕管理和
basically talk about what screen
基本上讲 什么屏幕
management is managing so first we have
管理层首先管理我们
screen management colon tab and first
屏幕管理冒号选项卡和第一
we're going to reference transition
我们将参考转换
transition is you know like an element
过渡是你知道的一个元素
of our screen manager okay so what we
我们的屏幕管理器 没关系，所以我们
inherited from to make our screen
从我们的屏幕继承而来
management class their transition you
管理类他们过渡你
guessed it we're going to use the fade
猜对了，我们打算 使用淡入淡出
transition then uh what are the screens
那么过渡到呃屏幕是什么
that we're managing will remain
我们正在管理的将保持
judging main screen and we're gonna
判断主屏幕 ，我们会
manage another screen okay and later on
管理另一个屏幕，以后再做
you might be able to add some stuff here
你可能可以 在这里 添加一些 东西
for now we'll just leave those actually
现在我们只是放弃 这些
completely blank so now let's create our
完全空白，现在让我们创建我们的
main screen rules here and um again TV
主屏幕规则在这里，再次 电视
files are not like spreadsheets Earths
文件不像电子表格地球
spreadsheets style sheets um in the
电子表格样式表 在这里
sense that you know like you reference
感觉你知道你 喜欢 你的参考
say an ID so main screen is our you know
说一个ID，所以主屏幕是我们你知道的
parent and then we've got this child you
父母，然后我们有这个孩子你
know ID basically and then we can pass
基本知道ID，然后我们可以通过
some more things and actually reference
一些更多的东西和实际参考
that ID and have a user scroll to that
该ID并让用户滚动到该位置
ID and all that kind of stuff it's kind
ID和所有那种东西都很友善
it's basically the same thing here so
它基本上是同样的事情， 所以 在这里
here we're gonna give it a name in the
这里我们要给它一个名字
name of main screen we're just gonna say
主屏幕的名称我们会说
is main and that's basically it and then
是主要的，这基本上是它 然后
we we want a budding here capital B for
我们我们要在这里发展一个资本B
button by the way we want a button tab
按钮的方式我们想要一个 按钮选项卡
over we're gonna have a few elements
在 我们就要有几个要素
here and what this button is going to do
这里以及这个按钮将要做什么
is on release which is a function of a
是在释放其的一个函数
button here on release what do we want
按钮在这里 释放我们想要什么
to happen well app dot root
发生好的应用程序点 根
dot current so our app is basically this
点电流， 所以我们的应用基本上是这样的
right main app and then we're saying
正确的主要应用程序，然后我们说
basically dot root dot current for the
基本上为点根电流为
current screen that we're looking at and
我们正在查看的当前屏幕
we want to actually change that to other
我们想要将其改变为其他
if the button is going to be the on so
如果按钮将是如此
the main screen and it would be like hey
主屏幕， 它会 像嘿
go to another page or go to these
转到其他页面或转到这些页面
settings or whatever basically this is
设置或基本上 是这样的
what controls what this button does so
什么控制一下这个按钮， 这样做
we want it to head to other for another
我们希望它能够转到另一个
page so the name of our say another
页面，所以我们说的另一个名字
screen for the IDE like the ID anyways
无论如何 ，这个IDE的屏幕就像ID一样
the name is going to be other so that's
这个名字将会是其他的
kind of how you reference them anyways
无论如何 ， 你如何引用它们
that's on release but we need a few
这是在发布，但我们需要一些
other things first of all we need some
首先我们需要一些 其他的 东西
text to let the user know what the heck
文本让用户知道这到底是什么
is about to happen well just look how
即将发生的只是看看如何
this actually next screen that's
这实际上是下一个屏幕
probably the easiest and then finally
可能最简单，然后最后
font size will just say 50 so it's nice
字体大小只会说50，所以它很好
and clear and that's basically it with
并且很清楚，基本上就是这样
the main screen and now we're going to
主屏幕，现在我们要
code the another screen I'm going to
代码中的另一个屏幕我要去
just copy this paste this
只需复制这个粘贴这个
instead of a main screen it is another
而不是主屏幕，这是另一个
screen name is other when we release the
当我们释放时，屏幕名称是其他
button on this screen we want to change
我们要更改 此屏幕上的按钮
back to the main screen and then of
回到主屏幕 然后
course this will say something about
当然这会说一些 关于
going back home so we'll just say back
回家后我们会回去
home okay easy enough and now we've got
家 很好很容易 ，现在我们已经有了
basically all of our required you know
基本上我们都需要你知道
TV stuff and we've got our buttons we've
电视的东西，我们有我们的按钮
got our screen manager managing our
让我们的屏幕管理者管理我们的
screens or screens are willing to change
屏幕或屏幕愿意改变
the current screen to other and the way
当前屏幕以其他方式呈现
that we're doing that is with a fade a
我们正在做的是淡化a
transition so I think we're ready to run
所以我认为我们已经 准备好 了
let's see if we have any errors so you
让我们看看我们是否有任何 错误，所以你
can run that our screen comes up short
可以运行，我们的屏幕出现短缺
off we have next screen we click on next
关闭，我们有下一个屏幕，我们点击下一步
screen and we see it faded to this
屏幕， 我们看到它淡入此
screen here we'll click it again and we
屏幕在这里， 我们将再次点击它 ，我们
go back home so we can see that this
回家后我们 可以看到这一点
basically worked the way that we at
基本上按照我们的方式工作
least for now have intended obviously
至少目前显然是有意的
the button is giant and we don't really
按钮是巨大的 ，我们并不真的
do anything else but we are able to go
做任何事情，但我们能够 去
back and forth between various screens
在各种屏幕之间来回移动
and then obviously as time goes on we
然后显然随着 时间的推移 我们
can add some information it's more you
可以添加一些信息， 这是你越
know kind of gooey stuffs logic here and
知道这里 的 粘性东西的逻辑和
then come into our actual TV file add
然后进入我们的 实际电视文件添加
some more kind of graphics and
一些更多类型的 图形和
customization and maybe not make the
定制，也许不会使
button take up the whole screen that
按钮占据整个屏幕
kind of stuff so we're gonna add stuff
一种东西， 所以我们要添加的 东西
there so I figured that most or the best
有那么我想 ，大多数 还是最好
thing to do now would be show since in
从现在 开始 ， 现在要做的事情 就是展示
the previous video we actually made an
以前的视频，我们实际上做了一个
application where we were drawing stuff
我们正在绘制东西的应用程序
right why not just add that application
为什么不 直接添加该应用程序？
as if it was you know anything else so
就好像它是你知道什么都 如此
we'll add that application will
我们将添加 该应用程序
basically come to the main screen we'll
基本上我们会来到主屏幕
hit this it'll come to our application
打这个它会来我们的应用程序
and then maybe there's a button that
然后也许有一个按钮，
heads us back home okay something simple
把我们带回家好吧简单一点
like that so that's what we're gonna
像 这样 ，这就是我们要去
cover in the next video so stay tuned
在下一个视频封面， 敬请期待
for that if you guys have any questions
因为 如果你们 有任何问题
or comments on this video please feel
或 对此视频的 评论 请感受
free to leave them below otherwise as
免费将他们留下，否则如下
always thanks for watching thanks for
总是感谢您收看 谢谢
all the support subscriptions until next
所有支持订阅，直到下一个
time
时间